Today we'll be touring this whimsical
luxury listing priced at
$899,000 in Temple,
Texas. Hi, I'm Andrea Dudik, realtor and
associate broker with Vista Real Estate,
and welcome back to Living in Central
Texas. If you're new to my channel,
don't forget to like this video,
subscribe, and click the bell icon so
that you can get more beautiful home
tours just like this and get some really
great information on moving to central
Texas. Okay, so today we're going to be
touring this really beautiful listing.
It's on 1.2 fully wooded acres. It has a
wet weather creek below. Um, it's really
nicely tucked away on a private drive,
so it feels very secluded, especially
with all these trees, but you're you
have really great access to everything.
You are 45 minutes away from Waco,
Texas, a good 30ish minutes from Fort
Kazos, and about an hour north from
Austin,
Texas. Welcome to 901 Hartrick Canyon
Drive, Temple, Texas. This home was
built in
1992 and is
3,417 square ft of beautiful and
functional living space. It is three
bedrooms, 2 and 1/2
bathrooms. It is in the Hartrick Bluff
development, and while it is in Temple,
Texas, it actually falls in the Academy
ISD school district. There is an HOA,
but it's $1,000 annual, so much less
than some other areas of the world.
What's really cool is that it's tucked
away inside of one of Temple's most
exclusive gated communities. There are
just eight residences in this gated
community. And with the really wooded
space, um, everything just feels super
private and you quite honestly don't
even know anyone else exists out here.
It's a truly rare combination of natural
beauty, a wonderful space, and peaceful
privacy. As we enter the home, you can
just feel how bright and inviting this
entire home is. They did a fantastic job
of adding all of these windows. And so,
you can basically see all of the trees
and nature from every room, especially
from the main living space here. There's
some luxury vinyl plank throughout the
main living spaces of this home. And
then you have two living areas and two
dining spaces, one of which is currently
used as an
office. You can also see in the kitchen,
maybe as you're doing dishes, being able
to look out on that back patio and look
out into nature. Something that I
thought was really neat was as I was
recording, there were multiple
hummingbirds feeding in the hummingbird
feeders. I saw multiple squirrels while
I was here. So, I can just imagine all
of the creatures and nature that you
would see if you owned this beautiful
piece of property. There is a seasonal
wet weather creek which is not super
full right now, but there are wonderful
pictures of it full and flowing.
The generous balconies and outdoor
living spaces provide for breathtaking
views overlooking this serene la land
landscape. You can just imagine sitting
out here enjoying a fire or even coffee
from your upstairs balcony in the
morning. All three bedrooms are
upstairs. Now, the carpet um is a little
dated, but you can really tell that
everything's been wellmaintained in this
home.
Downstairs in the laundry room, you'll
notice tons of additional cabinetry and
a utility sink. One of my favorite parts
of this home is the primary suite, which
has one of the most spectacular views of
the entire property and its own private
patio entrance.
While the primary ensuite is slightly
older, built in 1992, the layout is
super neat and functional. You have
closets on both sides with separate
vanities and of course the large soaking
tub overlooks the front of the home and
again all of the trees and nature from
the front and a separate shower.
There's a threecar garage which offers
plenty of room for storage, hobbies, or
vehicles. And of course, the gated
community offers not only security and
seclusion, but a shared common area
along the creek, ideal for family
gatherings or simply unwinding
outdoors. Photos do not do this home
justice, and you really should see it
for yourself.
If you're thinking about moving here, be
sure to download the free relocation
guide below. It's packed with
neighborhood statistics, videos, and
local
insights. Hey, thank you so much for
touring this awesome home at 901
Hartrick Canyon in Temple, Texas. This
was a super unique home that I was
really glad to show you because homes
like this don't come on the market every
day. If you are looking for a luxury
home with lots of space, um you can
really take advantage of an awesome
location, this
1.2 fully wooded acre lot with that
seasonal creek. It's just really cool.
You can come in, do all the updates that
you want to the home, make it exactly
like you want it, and get this awesome
property, the great location. And if you
would like any more information on this
home, if you would like to schedule a
private tour, you can find all my
contact information below. Till next
time.
[Music]